Guide to the Washington State University Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center Photographs 1919-1969
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 2: USDA Photographs, 1946-1952
  - 1950 hop selections. Hop yard - Irrigation Experiment Station. 5x7 neg. 1950-08-15 (Box 8, Item 50.006)
  - Erigaron Canadensis - aster yellows: Plant of E. canadensis naturally infected with aster yellows virus. Irrigatiion Experiment Station. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-12-01 (Box 8, Item 50.007)
  - Tomato - Dwarf and Curly top. Irrigation Experiment Station. Center plant is healthy check; 3 on L infected by grafting with tomato curly-top virus; 3 on $ with dwarf (green dwarf) virus from potato. Evidence for the identity of green dwarf and curly top. (Box 8, Item 50.008)
  - Tomato - big bud. Irrigation Experiment Station. Center plant is healthy check; 2 others infected with big bud by grafting from potato seedlings showing symptoms of purple top. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-12-01 (Box 8, Item 50.009)
  - Aster - yellows: Aster plant (Crego purple) grafted with scion of Erigeron canadensis infected with aster yellows. Aster plant shows greening of flowers and slanting. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-12-01 (Box 8, Item 50.010)
  - Map - Columbia Basin Project showing location of Development Farms. For Bulletin 520. 5x7 neg.; print. WSUP340. 1950 (Box 8, Item 50.011)
  - Winchester Farm Copywork. Basement iron. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-11 (Box 8, Item 50.012)
  - Ext.- Zn def beans, Lc -Zn def bean next to sprayed plot, Rc - Beans sprayed with ZnSO₄ on 7/7, R - normal beans. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1950-08-01 (Box 8, Item 50.013)
  - Copy work - Potatoes. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950 (Box 8, Item 50.014)
  - Copy work - Chlorotic Corn Stripe. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950 (Box 8, Item 50.015)
  - Copy work - Moses Lake Farm. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950 (Box 8, Item 50.016)
  - Copy work - Pasco Farm. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950 (Box 8, Item 50.017)
  - Map - Columbia Basin Project showing areas being farmed prior to 1948. The orchards of Hanford-White Bluffs area not shown because on 1948 they were destroyed by Atomic Energy Project. 5x7 neg.; print. 1950 (Box 8, Item 50.018)
  - Tomato - Dwarf (curly top?). Symptoms induced by grafting from "dormant seed piece" potato. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-01-23 (Box 8, Item 50.020)
  - Tomato - Big Bud. Induced by grafting from potato seedling showing symptoms of green dwarf? Photo 5 mos. after grafting. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-01-23 (Box 8, Item 50.021)
  - Tomato - Big Bud. Plant on R is affect, healthy on L. Disease induced by grafting from potato seedling from field. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-01-23 (Box 8, Item 50.022)
  - Tomato - dwarf. Disease induced by grafting from small shoots on dormant potato seed piece (seed piece failed to produce a plant during growing season). Plants grafted 12/14/48, cut back 12/28/49, old leaves removed 1/12/50. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-01 (Box 8, Item 50.023)
  - Tomato - Dwarf- induced by grafting from previously infected tomato. Both plants are affected. One on L shows least amount of dwarfing ever induced - may be something else involved. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-02-13 (Box 8, Item 50.024)
  - Tomato - Dwarf - range of symptoms induced by grafting. Photo taken 7 weeks after grafting. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-02-13 (Box 8, Item 50.025)
  - Tomato - Big Bud, induced by grafting, 7 weeks later. Plant in center is healthy. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-02-13 (Box 8, Item 50.026)
  - Tomato - Big Bud, induced by grafting from stunted shoots on potato. Grafted 12/26/49. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-02-13 (Box 8, Item 50.027)
  - Potato scab--Experiment P on scab control, 1949-50. Greenhouse. Treatment: 1. Na₂CO₃ plus, 2. Na₂CO₃ plus CaO 2.0 m.e./100 g., 3. Na₂CO₃ plus CaO 4.0 m.e./100 g., 4.Na₂CO₃ plus CaO 8.0 m.e./100 g., 5. Na₂CO₃ plus CaCO₃ 2.0 m.e./100 g., 6. Na₂CO₃ plus CaCO (Box 8, Item 50.028)
  - Tomato - soil fumigation 1949. Greenhouse experiment. Numbers refer to treatments. 2 4.75x3.75 negs.; prints. 1950-02-27 (Box 8, Item 50.029)
  - Potato scab - effect of pH and lime experiment P. Treatments: 1. Check, Na₂CO₃ alone, 4.CaO plus Na₂CO₃, 7. CaCO₃ plus Na₂CO₃, 10. CaSO₄ plus Na₂CO₃. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-04 (Box 8, Item 50.030)
  - Asparagus - cross section of young crown - healthy. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-05-18 (Box 8, Item 50.031)
  - Asparagus - young seedlings cut through crown to show habit of growth. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-05-18 (Box 8, Item 50.032)
  - Asparagus - cross section of crown several years old showing habit of growth. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-05-18 (Box 8, Item 50.033)
  - Asparagus - young seedlings showing habit of growth. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-05-18 (Box 8, Item 50.034)
  - Asparagus - Blue Mold Rot. Close-up of infected crown showing decay lesion. 2 4.75x3.75 negs.; prints. 1950-05-18 (Box 8, Item 50.035)
  - Alfalfa - Witches' Broom. Symptoms on various legumes. Illus. for paper with E.C.Klostermeyer made up and copied. Detail: Results of insect transmission tests on A. Sweet clover, B Med. Lupulina, C. Lathyrus sylvestris, D.Lorus corniculatus. 4.75x3.75 neg (Box 8, Item 50.036)
  - Pepper - Inoculated by grafting with big bug virus from tomato (originally from potato). May have leafroll also. 2 4.75x3.75 negs. 1950-07 (Box 8, Item 50.037)
  - Pepper - Inoculated with "dwarf" virus from tomato (originally from potato). Fruit is read prematurely and leaves yellow. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-07 (Box 8, Item 50.038)
  - Pepper - healthy plant for comparison with dwarf and big bud virus infections. Greenhouse grown. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-07 (Box 8, Item 50.039)
  - Potato - witches' broom plus leafroll. Also obtained big bud varus from this plant. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-07 (Box 8, Item 50.040)
  - Potato - witches' broom new tubers sprouting following inoculation with witches' broom by grafting from potato. 2 4.75x3.75 negs. 1950-07 (Box 8, Item 50.041)
  - Sorghum - Varieties, Moses Lake Development Farm. Glenn Miller shown. Glenn Miller. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. WSUP341. 1950-09 (Box 8, Item 50.042)
  - Weeds - 2,4-D injury. Fence row along N side of Development Farm, Moses Lake at end of airport runway (planes spraying weeds took off from this airport). 4.75x3.75 neg. 1950-09 (Box 8, Item 50.043)
  - Corn- fertility trial. Moses Lake Development Farm., 1950. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09 (Box 8, Item 50.044)
  - Moses Lake Development Farm. General view South to farm stead. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09 (Box 8, Item 50.045)
  - Sprinklers vs. disease. Experiment at Winchester Development Farm. Photo shows spread of Xanthemonas phaseoli with over-head sprinkling. Stakes mark location of inoculation. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09 (Box 8, Item 50.046)
  - Sprinklers vs. disease. Experiment at Winchester Development Farm. Photo shows spread of X. phaseoli on Red Mexican beans under sprinklers. Stakes mark location of original inoculation. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09 (Box 8, Item 50.047)
  - Sprinklers vs. disease. Experiment at Winchester Development Farm. Furrow irrigated plot of Red Mexican showing confinement of X. phaseoili to point of inoculation between stakes. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1950-09 (Box 8, Item 50.048)
  - Sorghum - factorial experiment Moses Lake Development Farm. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09 (Box 8, Item 50.049)
  - Potato - soil fumigation experiment. Rotation plots. Treatment: Chloropicrin plus 160# /a N, 120#/a P. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.050)
  - Potato - soil fumigation experiment. Rotation plots. Treatment: 120#/a P alone. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.051)
  - Potato - soil fumigation experiment. Rotation plots. Treatment: 160#/a N alone. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.052)
  - Potato - soil fumigation experiment. Rotation plots. Treatments: N 160#/ac, P 120#/ac. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.053)
  - Tomato - "Dwarf" variety Stokesdale. Grafted from potato seedling. P.S. 46.Grafted 6/27/50. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.054)
  - Tomato "Spotted wilt" type symptom on variety Souix induced by grafting from necrotic caleco on White Rose potato. Grafted 7/17/50. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.055)
  - Potato - Green Dwarf. Tuber trans symptom on potato from Gem plant grafted with dwarf from tomato originally taken from "dormant seed piece" potato. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.056)
  - Potato - Big Bud source, induced Big Bud when grafted on tomato. Shows severely dwarfed shoots with swollen bases. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.057)
  - Tomato - healthy variety Stokesdale for comparison with diseased plants. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.058)
  - Tomato - Big Bud, variety Stockesdale from seedling potato S.P.-3. Grafted 6/27/50. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.059)
  - Tomato - Big Bud on variety Stockesdale from potato seedling P.S.-3. Grafted 6/27/50. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.060)
  - Potato Green Dwarf (?) from field. 4 different 4.75x3.75 negatives, plus 1 healthy. Prints. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.061)
  - Potato - soil fumigation experiment plots. Rotation plots. Treatment check. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.062)
  - Potato - soil fumigation experiment. Rotation plots. Plot - Chloropicrin along, 50 ga./ac. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.063)
  - Potato - Late breaking virus? From field grown Netted Gem. Grafted to tomato - Graft #348. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09-18 (Box 8, Item 50.064)
  - Potato - Purple-top? Seedling no. -UP45. Photographed in field. Grafted to tomato in greenhouse #360. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-09-22 (Box 8, Item 50.068)
  - Beans - Sclerotinia rot commercial planting on new ground at Development Farm, Pasco. Variety Red Mexican. This field had several such infection centers up to 8 - 10' in diameter. Furrow irrigation. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-10 (Box 8, Item 50.069)
  - Sprinklers vs. disease. Experiment at Winchester Development Farm. General view of furrow irrigated Red Mexican beans inocculated at 2 points with common bacterial blight. No spread occurred. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-10 (Box 8, Item 50.070)
  - Beans - bacterial blight - large field of Red Mexicans on Pasco Unit. Photo is supposed to show general bacterial blight infection resulting from sprinkling. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-10 (Box 8, Item 50.071)
  - Aster yellows on Horse weed. Erigeron canadensis plants showing various stages of infection with aster yellows virus. Ditchbank on Pasco Project. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-10 (Box 8, Item 50.072)
  - Experiment G-21, Timmerman 22-36". Left-no iron, Center-iron nitrate, Right- applied in soil 2/3. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-02-13 (Box 8, Item 50.073)
  - Less lodging of corn. Field F2, South end plot 516. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-11-03 (Box 8, Item 50.075)
  - More corn lodging. F2, South end plot 611. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1950-11-03 (Box 8, Item 50.076)
  - Aster-Yellows or Phyllody. Plant infected by dodder transfer of tomato big bud virus. Virus in tomato by graft inoculation from purple-top potato. Dodder was cuscuta sabinclusa. 3 4.75x3.75 negs. Print. 1951-02-31 (Box 8, Item 51.001)
  - Aster-Yellows. Plant infected by dodder transfer of tomato big bud virus. Virus in tomato by graft inoculation from purple-top potato. Dodder used - cuscuta sabinclusa. 2 4.75x3.75 negs.; prints. 1951-02-26 (Box 8, Item 51.002)
  - Potato - Alternaria rot. In seed from Nash, Montana. Isolations positive - No. 197. 2 4.75x3.75 negs.; prints. 1951-03-26 (Box 8, Item 51.003)
  - Potato - Alternaria rot. Seed from Nash, Montana. Isolations No. 197. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-03-26 (Box 8, Item 51.004)
  - Potato - Alternaria rot. Seed from Nash, Montana. Isolations No. 197. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-03-26 (Box 8, Item 51.005)
  - Potato - Mahogany browning? Seed potato from Montana. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-03-26 (Box 8, Item 51.006)
  - Potato - Mahogany browning? White Rose from Montana. Some lesions near surface are alternaria rot. Deep discoloration is similar to mahogany browning. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-03-26 (Box 8, Item 51.007)
  - Potato - stem end necrosis. In Netted Gem seed from Montana. No fungi (isolation No. 196). Not net necrosis. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-03-26 (Box 8, Item 51.008)
  - Potato - Jelly end? Small tuber (White Rose) seed from Troutdale, OR. Isolation No. 195 - negative. Defect extended entire length of tuber, confined to vascular ring. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-03-15 (Box 8, Item 51.009)
  - Potato - Internal brown spot. Not definite whether this as a type of cold injury or the physiologic brown spot. Isolations negative. Tuber from Western WA certified seed. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-03-26 (Box 8, Item 51.010)
  - Potato - "Flack necrosis" (my term) Common in 1950 seed from coastal areas of OR, WA, B.C. Isolations negative. 2 4.75x3.75 negs. Prints. 1951-03-15 (Box 8, Item 51.011)
  - G-29 Columbia Basin Soils. Alfalfa 2nd cut. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 8, Item 51.012)
  - G-29 Columbia Basin Soils. Alfalfa 2nd cut. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 8, Item 51.013)
  - G-29 Columbia Basin Soils. Alfalfa 2nd cut. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 8, Item 51.014)
  - G-29 Columbia Basin Soils. Alfalfa 2nd cut. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 8, Item 51.015)
  - G-29 Columbia Basin Soils. Alfalfa 2nd cut. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 8, Item 51.016)
  - G-29 Columbia Basin Soils. Alfalfa 2nd cut. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 8, Item 51.017)
  - G-29 Columbia Basin Soils. Alfalfa 2nd cut. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 8, Item 51.018)
  - G-29 Columbia Basin Soils. Alfalfa 2nd cut. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 8, Item 51.019)
  - Moses Lake wheat nursery. Moses Lake ,Washington. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-06 (Box 8, Item 51.020)
  - Moses Lake oat nursery. Moses Lake ,Washington. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1951-06 (Box 8, Item 51.021)
  - Field of beans. Moses Lake. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-07-12 (Box 8, Item 51.022)
  - Potato - Black root - fungus superficiaol - a sp. of Ceratostonia. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-10 (Box 8, Item 51.023)
  - Potato - White Rose - local lesions on new leaves following grafting with tomato curly top from field. Tobacco mosaic contaminant?. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-10 (Box 8, Item 51.024)
  - Dodder - Big Bud. White background. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1951-11-30 (Box 8, Item 51.025)
  - Dodder - (C. Campestris) with symptoms of big bud - each specimen represents a single flower -. Bottom row healthy. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-11-30 (Box 8, Item 51.026)
  - Potato - White Rose, local lesions on unino. Leaves following grafting with tomato (curly top) from field. Tobacco mosaic. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951 (Box 8, Item 51.027)
  - Potato - leaf roll - chronic stage Russet Burbank. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-07 (Box 8, Item 51.028)
  - Bean - rust.Composite picture of various types of injury. Rust collected on Pasco unit Allen Udlinck farm. 2 4.75x3.75 negs.; prints. 1951-09-12 (Box 8, Item 51.029)
  - Purple Top on var. Ontario. Scions to Stokesdale tomato transmitted big bud. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-09 (Box 8, Item 51.030)
  - Potato Green Dwarf - current season symptoms on Netted Gem. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1951-09-12 (Box 8, Item 51.031)
  - Potato - healthy shoot, for comparison with Green dwarf specimens. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-09-12 (Box 8, Item 51.032)
  - Petunia - virescence of blossom - close-up of several blooms. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1951-09-12 (Box 8, Item 51.033)
  - Potato - green dwarf, current season infection on Netted Gem potato. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-09-12 (Box 8, Item 51.034)
  - Potato - Green dwarf, moderate state of current season infection. Netted Gem. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-09-12 (Box 8, Item 51.035)
  - Potato - healthy shoot, for comparison with green dwarf. Netted Gem. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1951-09-12 (Box 8, Item 51.036)
  - Potato - green dwarf - current season infection - mild stage. Netted Gem. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-09-12 (Box 8, Item 51.037)
  - Petunia - virescence of blossom. Flowers are dwarfed and greenish instead of purple. Collected in Prosser. Nothing trans to tomato - physiologic?. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-09-12 (Box 8, Item 51.038)
  - Erigeron canadensis - Yellows - Healthy (right) and infected left. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-09-12 (Box 8, Item 51.039)
  - Green dwarf - Natural field infection. Moderate symptoms. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-08 (Box 8, Item 51.040)
  - Potato - purple-top on seedling variety, transmitted big bud to tomato. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-09 (Box 8, Item 51.041)
  - Water weeds. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1951 (Box 8, Item 51.042)
  - Water weeds. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1951 (Box 8, Item 51.043)
  - Chara. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1951 (Box 8, Item 51.044)
  - Cosmos - Phyllody - aster yellows or big bud?. Pasco Development Farm. 4.75x3.75 neg. 1951-09 (Box 8, Item 51.045)
  - Mullein - Verbascum thapsis - Phyllody on. Mabton,. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-09 (Box 8, Item 51.046)
  - Tomato - Big Bud - natural infection from field. Pasco Development Farm. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-09 (Box 8, Item 51.047)
  - Dodder - big bud on. Close-up of blossoms. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-11-30 (Box 8, Item 51.048)
  - Dodder - C. campestris - Big Bud on. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-11-30 (Box 8, Item 51.049)
  - Dodder - Cuscuta campestris with symptoms of big bud. Dodder was grown for 2 months on Stokesdale tomato plant inoculated with big bud from potato. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-11-30 (Box 8, Item 51.050)
  - Zinc deficient bean plants. Roza B45. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-09 (Box 8, Item 51.052)
  - Zinc deficient bean plants. Roza B45. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-09 (Box 8, Item 51.053)
  - Zinc deficient Red Mexican bean plants. Roza B45. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-09 (Box 8, Item 51.054)
  - Carrot - root malformation resulting from us of P162 @ 6 gals/ac. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1952-11 (Box 8, Item 52.001)
  - Erigeron canadensis - Yellows disease on terminals. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1952-08 (Box 8, Item 52.002)
  - Ladino - Phyllody on individual shoot. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1952-08 (Box 8, Item 52.003)
  - Ladino clover - healthy shoot. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. WSUP342. 1952-08 (Box 8, Item 52.004)
  - Ladino clover - showing various stages of phyllody of blossoms, 2 plants on left are healthy. Isolations No. 197. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1952-08 (Box 8, Item 52.005)
  - Egg plant - control of verticillium wilt with Julius Hyman compound - P-162. Comparison of check and 20 ppm. Healthy on left, diseased on right. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1952-02 (Box 8, Item 52.006)
  - Egg plant - control of verticillium wilt with Compound - P-162. Seeds were planted 12/17/51. (Planted 70 days old.) Picture shows check, 10 ppm and 20 ppm. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. WSUP343. 1952-02 (Box 8, Item 52.007)
  - Egg plant - control of verticillium wilt with Compound - P-162. Plants 70 days old. Shows check, 30 ppm and 40 ppm. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1952-02 (Box 8, Item 52.008)
  - Egg plant - control of verticillium wilt with Julius Hyman compound P-162. Comparison of check and 10 ppm. Healthy plants on left, vert. infected on right. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1952-02 (Box 8, Item 52.009)
  - Egg plant - control of verticillium wilt with Julius Hyman Co. compound P-162. From left to right 40, 30, 20, 10, 5 ppm. respectively and check. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1952-02-18 (Box 8, Item 52.010)
  - Beans - P162 injury on whole plants of Red Mexican. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-08 (Box 8, Item 52.011)
  - Beans - P162 injury to Red Mexican. Healthy and typically injured plants. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-08 (Box 8, Item 52.012)
  - Beans - P162 injury on leaves of Red Mexican beans - Inj. 6 gal. per acre. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-08 (Box 8, Item 52.013)
  - Datura - Healthy plant for comparison with Big Bud infected plant shown in Negative No. 52-15. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-02 (Box 8, Item 52.014)
  - Datura - Infected with big bud virus. Virus obtained from potato 9/18/51 into tomato (Graft 677a) grafted into D. Stramonium 11/13/51. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1951-02 (Box 8, Item 52.015)
  - Dodder - Big Bud - Photo of sketches showing stages of phyllody. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1952 (Box 8, Item 52.016)
  - Undetermined Ornamental - phyllody. 4.75x3.75 neg.; print. 1952-08 (Box 8, Item 52.017)
- Series 3: Index Cards
  - 78 WSU-Prosser descriptive index cards (series 1). (Box 8)
  - 17 USDA descriptive index cards (series 2). (Box 8)